[
    {
        "Front": "会う",
        "Back": "to meet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "Front": "青",
        "Back": "blue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "Front": "青い",
        "Back": "blue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "Front": "赤",
        "Back": "red",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "Front": "赤い",
        "Back": "red",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 4
    },
    {
        "Front": "明い",
        "Back": "bright",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 5
    },
    {
        "Front": "秋",
        "Back": "autumn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 6
    },
    {
        "Front": "開く",
        "Back": "to open,to become open",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 7
    },
    {
        "Front": "開ける",
        "Back": "to open",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 8
    },
    {
        "Front": "上げる",
        "Back": "to give",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 9
    },
    {
        "Front": "朝",
        "Back": "morning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 10
    },
    {
        "Front": "朝御飯",
        "Back": "breakfast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 11
    },
    {
        "Front": "あさって",
        "Back": "day after tomorrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "足",
        "Back": "foot,leg",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 12
    },
    {
        "Front": "明日",
        "Back": "tomorrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 13
    },
    {
        "Front": "あそこ",
        "Back": "over there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "遊ぶ",
        "Back": "to play,to make a visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 14
    },
    {
        "Front": "暖かい",
        "Back": "warm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 15
    },
    {
        "Front": "頭",
        "Back": "head",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 16
    },
    {
        "Front": "新しい",
        "Back": "new",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 17
    },
    {
        "Front": "あちら",
        "Back": "there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "暑い",
        "Back": "hot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 18
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱い",
        "Back": "hot to the touch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 19
    },
    {
        "Front": "厚い",
        "Back": "kind, deep, thick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 20
    },
    {
        "Front": "あっち",
        "Back": "over there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "後",
        "Back": "afterwards",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 21
    },
    {
        "Front": "あなた",
        "Back": "you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "兄",
        "Back": "(humble) older brother",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 22
    },
    {
        "Front": "姉",
        "Back": "(humble) older sister",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 23
    },
    {
        "Front": "あの",
        "Back": "that over there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アパート",
        "Back": "apartment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あびる",
        "Back": "to bathe,to shower",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "危ない",
        "Back": "dangerous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 24
    },
    {
        "Front": "甘い",
        "Back": "sweet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 25
    },
    {
        "Front": "あまり",
        "Back": "not very",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "雨",
        "Back": "rain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 26
    },
    {
        "Front": "飴",
        "Back": "candy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 27
    },
    {
        "Front": "洗う",
        "Back": "to wash",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 28
    },
    {
        "Front": "ある",
        "Back": "to be,to have (used for inanimate objects)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "歩く",
        "Back": "to walk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 29
    },
    {
        "Front": "あれ",
        "Back": "that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いい/よい",
        "Back": "good",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いいえ",
        "Back": "no",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "言う",
        "Back": "to say",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 30
    },
    {
        "Front": "家",
        "Back": "house",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 31
    },
    {
        "Front": "いかが",
        "Back": "how",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "行く",
        "Back": "to go",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 32
    },
    {
        "Front": "いくつ",
        "Back": "how many?,how old?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いくら",
        "Back": "how much?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "池",
        "Back": "pond",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 33
    },
    {
        "Front": "医者",
        "Back": "medical doctor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 34
    },
    {
        "Front": "いす",
        "Back": "chair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "忙しい",
        "Back": "busy,irritated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 35
    },
    {
        "Front": "痛い",
        "Back": "painful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 36
    },
    {
        "Front": "一",
        "Back": "one",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 37
    },
    {
        "Front": "一日",
        "Back": "(1) one day, (2) first of month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 38
    },
    {
        "Front": "いちばん",
        "Back": "best,first",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いつ",
        "Back": "when",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "五日",
        "Back": "five days, fifth day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 39
    },
    {
        "Front": "一緒",
        "Back": "together",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 40
    },
    {
        "Front": "五つ",
        "Back": "five",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 41
    },
    {
        "Front": "いつも",
        "Back": "always",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "犬",
        "Back": "dog",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 42
    },
    {
        "Front": "今",
        "Back": "now",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 43
    },
    {
        "Front": "意味",
        "Back": "meaning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 44
    },
    {
        "Front": "妹",
        "Back": "(humble) younger sister",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 45
    },
    {
        "Front": "嫌",
        "Back": "unpleasant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 46
    },
    {
        "Front": "入口",
        "Back": "entrance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 47
    },
    {
        "Front": "居る",
        "Back": "to be, to have (used for people and animals)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 48
    },
    {
        "Front": "要る",
        "Back": "to need",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 49
    },
    {
        "Front": "入れる",
        "Back": "to put in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 50
    },
    {
        "Front": "色",
        "Back": "colour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 51
    },
    {
        "Front": "いろいろ",
        "Back": "various",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "上",
        "Back": "on top of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 52
    },
    {
        "Front": "後ろ",
        "Back": "behind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 53
    },
    {
        "Front": "薄い",
        "Back": "thin,weak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 54
    },
    {
        "Front": "歌",
        "Back": "song",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 55
    },
    {
        "Front": "歌う",
        "Back": "to sing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 56
    },
    {
        "Front": "生まれる",
        "Back": "to be born",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 57
    },
    {
        "Front": "海",
        "Back": "sea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 58
    },
    {
        "Front": "売る",
        "Back": "to sell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 59
    },
    {
        "Front": "煩い",
        "Back": "noisy,annoying",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 60
    },
    {
        "Front": "上着",
        "Back": "jacket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 61
    },
    {
        "Front": "絵",
        "Back": "picture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 62
    },
    {
        "Front": "映画",
        "Back": "movie",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 63
    },
    {
        "Front": "映画館",
        "Back": "cinema",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 64
    },
    {
        "Front": "英語",
        "Back": "English language",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 65
    },
    {
        "Front": "ええ",
        "Back": "yes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "駅",
        "Back": "station",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 66
    },
    {
        "Front": "エレベーター",
        "Back": "elevator",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉛筆",
        "Back": "pencil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 67
    },
    {
        "Front": "おいしい",
        "Back": "delicious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "多い",
        "Back": "many",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 68
    },
    {
        "Front": "大きい",
        "Back": "big",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 69
    },
    {
        "Front": "大きな",
        "Back": "big",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 70
    },
    {
        "Front": "大勢",
        "Back": "great number of people",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 71
    },
    {
        "Front": "お母さん",
        "Back": "(honorable) mother",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 72
    },
    {
        "Front": "お菓子",
        "Back": "sweets, candy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 73
    },
    {
        "Front": "お金",
        "Back": "money",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 74
    },
    {
        "Front": "起きる",
        "Back": "to get up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 75
    },
    {
        "Front": "置く",
        "Back": "to put",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 76
    },
    {
        "Front": "奥さん",
        "Back": "(honorable) wife",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 77
    },
    {
        "Front": "お酒",
        "Back": "alcohol, rice wine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 78
    },
    {
        "Front": "お皿",
        "Back": "plate, dish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 79
    },
    {
        "Front": "伯父/叔父",
        "Back": "grandfather,male senior citizen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 80
    },
    {
        "Front": "教える",
        "Back": "to teach,to tell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 81
    },
    {
        "Front": "押す",
        "Back": "to push, to stamp something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 82
    },
    {
        "Front": "遅い",
        "Back": "late,slow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 83
    },
    {
        "Front": "お茶",
        "Back": "green tea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 84
    },
    {
        "Front": "お手洗い",
        "Back": "bathroom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 85
    },
    {
        "Front": "お父さん",
        "Back": "(honorable) father",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 86
    },
    {
        "Front": "弟",
        "Back": "younger brother",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 87
    },
    {
        "Front": "男",
        "Back": "man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 88
    },
    {
        "Front": "男の子",
        "Back": "boy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 89
    },
    {
        "Front": "一昨日",
        "Back": "day before yesterday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 90
    },
    {
        "Front": "一昨年",
        "Back": "year before last",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 91
    },
    {
        "Front": "大人",
        "Back": "adult",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 92
    },
    {
        "Front": "おなか",
        "Back": "stomach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "同じ",
        "Back": "same",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 93
    },
    {
        "Front": "お兄さん",
        "Back": "(honorable) older brother",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 94
    },
    {
        "Front": "お姉さん",
        "Back": "(honorable) older sister",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 95
    },
    {
        "Front": "おばあさん",
        "Back": "grandmother,female senior-citizen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "伯母さん/叔母さん",
        "Back": "aunt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 96
    },
    {
        "Front": "お風呂",
        "Back": "bath",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 97
    },
    {
        "Front": "お弁当",
        "Back": "boxed lunch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 98
    },
    {
        "Front": "覚える",
        "Back": "to remember",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 99
    },
    {
        "Front": "おまわりさん",
        "Back": "friendly term for policeman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "重い",
        "Back": "heavy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 100
    },
    {
        "Front": "おもしろい",
        "Back": "interesting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "泳ぐ",
        "Back": "to swim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 101
    },
    {
        "Front": "降りる",
        "Back": "to get off, to descend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 102
    },
    {
        "Front": "終る",
        "Back": "to finish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 103
    },
    {
        "Front": "音楽",
        "Back": "music",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 104
    },
    {
        "Front": "女",
        "Back": "woman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 105
    },
    {
        "Front": "女の子",
        "Back": "girl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 106
    },
    {
        "Front": "外国",
        "Back": "foreign country",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 107
    },
    {
        "Front": "外国人",
        "Back": "foreigner",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 108
    },
    {
        "Front": "会社",
        "Back": "company",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 109
    },
    {
        "Front": "階段",
        "Back": "stairs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 110
    },
    {
        "Front": "買い物",
        "Back": "shopping",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 111
    },
    {
        "Front": "買う",
        "Back": "to buy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 112
    },
    {
        "Front": "返す",
        "Back": "to return something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 113
    },
    {
        "Front": "帰る",
        "Back": "to go back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 114
    },
    {
        "Front": "かかる",
        "Back": "to take time or money",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "かぎ",
        "Back": "key",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "書く",
        "Back": "to write",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 115
    },
    {
        "Front": "学生",
        "Back": "student",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 116
    },
    {
        "Front": "かける",
        "Back": "to call by phone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "傘",
        "Back": "umbrella",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 117
    },
    {
        "Front": "貸す",
        "Back": "to lend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 118
    },
    {
        "Front": "風",
        "Back": "wind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 119
    },
    {
        "Front": "風邪",
        "Back": "a cold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 120
    },
    {
        "Front": "家族",
        "Back": "family",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 121
    },
    {
        "Front": "方",
        "Back": "person, way of doing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 122
    },
    {
        "Front": "学校",
        "Back": "school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 123
    },
    {
        "Front": "カップ",
        "Back": "cup",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "家庭",
        "Back": "household",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 124
    },
    {
        "Front": "角",
        "Back": "a corner",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 125
    },
    {
        "Front": "かばん",
        "Back": "bag,basket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "花瓶",
        "Back": "a vase",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 126
    },
    {
        "Front": "紙",
        "Back": "paper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 127
    },
    {
        "Front": "カメラ",
        "Back": "camera",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "火曜日",
        "Back": "Tuesday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 128
    },
    {
        "Front": "辛い",
        "Back": "spicy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 129
    },
    {
        "Front": "体",
        "Back": "body",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 130
    },
    {
        "Front": "借りる",
        "Back": "to borrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 131
    },
    {
        "Front": "軽い",
        "Back": "light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 132
    },
    {
        "Front": "カレー",
        "Back": "curry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "カレンダー",
        "Back": "calendar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "川/河",
        "Back": "river",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 133
    },
    {
        "Front": "かわいい",
        "Back": "cute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "漢字",
        "Back": "Chinese character",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 134
    },
    {
        "Front": "木",
        "Back": "tree,wood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 135
    },
    {
        "Front": "黄色",
        "Back": "yellow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 136
    },
    {
        "Front": "黄色い",
        "Back": "yellow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 137
    },
    {
        "Front": "消える",
        "Back": "to disappear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 138
    },
    {
        "Front": "聞く",
        "Back": "to hear,to listen to,to ask",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 139
    },
    {
        "Front": "北",
        "Back": "north",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 140
    },
    {
        "Front": "ギター",
        "Back": "guitar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "汚い",
        "Back": "dirty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 141
    },
    {
        "Front": "喫茶店",
        "Back": "coffee lounge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 142
    },
    {
        "Front": "切手",
        "Back": "postage stamp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 143
    },
    {
        "Front": "切符",
        "Back": "ticket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 144
    },
    {
        "Front": "昨日",
        "Back": "yesterday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 145
    },
    {
        "Front": "九",
        "Back": "nine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 146
    },
    {
        "Front": "牛肉",
        "Back": "beef",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 147
    },
    {
        "Front": "牛乳",
        "Back": "milk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 148
    },
    {
        "Front": "今日",
        "Back": "today",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 149
    },
    {
        "Front": "教室",
        "Back": "classroom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 150
    },
    {
        "Front": "兄弟",
        "Back": "(humble) siblings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 151
    },
    {
        "Front": "去年",
        "Back": "last year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 152
    },
    {
        "Front": "嫌い",
        "Back": "hate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 153
    },
    {
        "Front": "切る",
        "Back": "to cut",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 154
    },
    {
        "Front": "着る",
        "Back": "to put on from the shoulders down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 155
    },
    {
        "Front": "きれい",
        "Back": "pretty,clean",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "キロ/キログラム",
        "Back": "kilogram",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "キロ/キロメートル",
        "Back": "kilometre",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "銀行",
        "Back": "bank",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 156
    },
    {
        "Front": "金曜日",
        "Back": "Friday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 157
    },
    {
        "Front": "薬",
        "Back": "medicine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 158
    },
    {
        "Front": "ください",
        "Back": "please",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "果物",
        "Back": "fruit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 159
    },
    {
        "Front": "口",
        "Back": "mouth,opening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 160
    },
    {
        "Front": "靴",
        "Back": "shoes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 161
    },
    {
        "Front": "靴下",
        "Back": "socks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 162
    },
    {
        "Front": "国",
        "Back": "country",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 163
    },
    {
        "Front": "曇り",
        "Back": "cloudy weather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 164
    },
    {
        "Front": "曇る",
        "Back": "to become cloudy,to become dim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 165
    },
    {
        "Front": "暗い",
        "Back": "gloomy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 166
    },
    {
        "Front": "クラス",
        "Back": "class",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "グラム",
        "Back": "gram",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "来る",
        "Back": "to come",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 167
    },
    {
        "Front": "車",
        "Back": "car,vehicle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 168
    },
    {
        "Front": "黒",
        "Back": "black",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 169
    },
    {
        "Front": "黒い",
        "Back": "black",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 170
    },
    {
        "Front": "警官",
        "Back": "policeman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 171
    },
    {
        "Front": "今朝",
        "Back": "this morning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 172
    },
    {
        "Front": "消す",
        "Back": "to erase,to turn off power",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 173
    },
    {
        "Front": "結構",
        "Back": "splendid,enough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 174
    },
    {
        "Front": "結婚",
        "Back": "marriage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 175
    },
    {
        "Front": "月曜日",
        "Back": "Monday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 176
    },
    {
        "Front": "玄関",
        "Back": "entry hall",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 177
    },
    {
        "Front": "元気",
        "Back": "health, vitality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 178
    },
    {
        "Front": "五",
        "Back": "five",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 179
    },
    {
        "Front": "公園",
        "Back": "park",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 180
    },
    {
        "Front": "交差点",
        "Back": "intersection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 181
    },
    {
        "Front": "紅茶",
        "Back": "black tea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 182
    },
    {
        "Front": "交番",
        "Back": "police box",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 183
    },
    {
        "Front": "声",
        "Back": "voice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 184
    },
    {
        "Front": "コート",
        "Back": "coat,tennis court",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コーヒー",
        "Back": "coffee",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ここ",
        "Back": "here",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "午後",
        "Back": "afternoon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 185
    },
    {
        "Front": "九日",
        "Back": "nine days, ninth day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 186
    },
    {
        "Front": "九つ",
        "Back": "nine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 187
    },
    {
        "Front": "午前",
        "Back": "morning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 188
    },
    {
        "Front": "答える",
        "Back": "to answer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 189
    },
    {
        "Front": "こちら",
        "Back": "this person or way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "こっち",
        "Back": "this person or way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コップ",
        "Back": "a glass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "今年",
        "Back": "this year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 190
    },
    {
        "Front": "言葉",
        "Back": "word,language",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 191
    },
    {
        "Front": "子供",
        "Back": "child",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 192
    },
    {
        "Front": "この",
        "Back": "this",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "御飯",
        "Back": "cooked rice,meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 193
    },
    {
        "Front": "コピーする",
        "Back": "to copy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "困る",
        "Back": "to be worried",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 194
    },
    {
        "Front": "これ",
        "Back": "this",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "今月",
        "Back": "this month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 195
    },
    {
        "Front": "今週",
        "Back": "this week",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 196
    },
    {
        "Front": "こんな",
        "Back": "such",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "今晩",
        "Back": "this evening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 197
    },
    {
        "Front": "さあ",
        "Back": "well…",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "財布",
        "Back": "wallet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 198
    },
    {
        "Front": "魚",
        "Back": "fish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 199
    },
    {
        "Front": "先",
        "Back": "the future,previous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 200
    },
    {
        "Front": "咲く",
        "Back": "to bloom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 201
    },
    {
        "Front": "作文",
        "Back": "composition,writing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 202
    },
    {
        "Front": "差す",
        "Back": "to stretch out hands,to raise an umbrella",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 203
    },
    {
        "Front": "雑誌",
        "Back": "magazine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 204
    },
    {
        "Front": "砂糖",
        "Back": "sugar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 205
    },
    {
        "Front": "寒い",
        "Back": "cold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 206
    },
    {
        "Front": "さ来年",
        "Back": "year after next",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 207
    },
    {
        "Front": "三",
        "Back": "three",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 208
    },
    {
        "Front": "散歩",
        "Back": "to stroll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 209
    },
    {
        "Front": "四",
        "Back": "four",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 210
    },
    {
        "Front": "塩",
        "Back": "salt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 211
    },
    {
        "Front": "しかし",
        "Back": "however",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "時間",
        "Back": "time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 212
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕事",
        "Back": "job",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 213
    },
    {
        "Front": "辞書",
        "Back": "dictionary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 214
    },
    {
        "Front": "静か",
        "Back": "quiet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 215
    },
    {
        "Front": "下",
        "Back": "below",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 216
    },
    {
        "Front": "七",
        "Back": "seven",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 217
    },
    {
        "Front": "質問",
        "Back": "question",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 218
    },
    {
        "Front": "自転車",
        "Back": "bicycle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 219
    },
    {
        "Front": "自動車",
        "Back": "automobile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 220
    },
    {
        "Front": "死ぬ",
        "Back": "to die",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 221
    },
    {
        "Front": "字引",
        "Back": "dictionary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 222
    },
    {
        "Front": "自分",
        "Back": "oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 223
    },
    {
        "Front": "閉まる",
        "Back": "to close,to be closed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 224
    },
    {
        "Front": "閉める",
        "Back": "to close something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 225
    },
    {
        "Front": "締める",
        "Back": "to tie",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 226
    },
    {
        "Front": "じゃ/じゃあ",
        "Back": "well then…",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "写真",
        "Back": "photograph",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 227
    },
    {
        "Front": "シャツ",
        "Back": "shirt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "シャワー",
        "Back": "shower",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "十",
        "Back": "ten",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 228
    },
    {
        "Front": "授業",
        "Back": "lesson,class work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 229
    },
    {
        "Front": "宿題",
        "Back": "homework",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 230
    },
    {
        "Front": "上手",
        "Back": "skillful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 231
    },
    {
        "Front": "丈夫",
        "Back": "strong,durable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 232
    },
    {
        "Front": "しょうゆ",
        "Back": "soy sauce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "食堂",
        "Back": "dining hall",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 233
    },
    {
        "Front": "知る",
        "Back": "to know",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 234
    },
    {
        "Front": "白",
        "Back": "white",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 235
    },
    {
        "Front": "白い",
        "Back": "white",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 236
    },
    {
        "Front": "新聞",
        "Back": "newspaper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 237
    },
    {
        "Front": "水曜日",
        "Back": "Wednesday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 238
    },
    {
        "Front": "吸う",
        "Back": "to smoke,to suck",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 239
    },
    {
        "Front": "スカート",
        "Back": "skirt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "好き",
        "Back": "likeable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 240
    },
    {
        "Front": "少ない",
        "Back": "a few",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 241
    },
    {
        "Front": "すぐに",
        "Back": "instantly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "少し",
        "Back": "few",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 242
    },
    {
        "Front": "涼しい",
        "Back": "refreshing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 243
    },
    {
        "Front": "ストーブ",
        "Back": "heater",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スプーン",
        "Back": "spoon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スポーツ",
        "Back": "sport",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ズボン",
        "Back": "trousers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "住む",
        "Back": "to live in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 244
    },
    {
        "Front": "スリッパ",
        "Back": "slippers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "する",
        "Back": "to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "座る",
        "Back": "to sit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 245
    },
    {
        "Front": "背",
        "Back": "height,stature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 246
    },
    {
        "Front": "生徒",
        "Back": "pupil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 247
    },
    {
        "Front": "セーター",
        "Back": "sweater,jumper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "せっけん",
        "Back": "economy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "背広",
        "Back": "business suit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 248
    },
    {
        "Front": "狭い",
        "Back": "narrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 249
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゼロ",
        "Back": "zero",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "千",
        "Back": "thousand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 250
    },
    {
        "Front": "先月",
        "Back": "last month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 251
    },
    {
        "Front": "先週",
        "Back": "last week",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 252
    },
    {
        "Front": "先生",
        "Back": "teacher,doctor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 253
    },
    {
        "Front": "洗濯",
        "Back": "washing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 254
    },
    {
        "Front": "全部",
        "Back": "all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 255
    },
    {
        "Front": "掃除",
        "Back": "to clean, to sweep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 256
    },
    {
        "Front": "そうして/そして",
        "Back": "and",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そこ",
        "Back": "that place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そちら",
        "Back": "over there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そっち",
        "Back": "over there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "外",
        "Back": "outside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 257
    },
    {
        "Front": "その",
        "Back": "that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そば",
        "Back": "near,beside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "空",
        "Back": "sky",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 258
    },
    {
        "Front": "それ",
        "Back": "that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それから",
        "Back": "after that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それでは",
        "Back": "in that situation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "大学",
        "Back": "university",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 259
    },
    {
        "Front": "大使館",
        "Back": "embassy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 260
    },
    {
        "Front": "大丈夫",
        "Back": "all right",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 261
    },
    {
        "Front": "大好き",
        "Back": "to be very likeable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 262
    },
    {
        "Front": "大切",
        "Back": "important",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 263
    },
    {
        "Front": "台所",
        "Back": "kitchen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 264
    },
    {
        "Front": "たいへん",
        "Back": "very",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "高い",
        "Back": "tall, expensive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 265
    },
    {
        "Front": "たくさん",
        "Back": "many",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タクシー",
        "Back": "taxi",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "出す",
        "Back": "to put out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 266
    },
    {
        "Front": "立つ",
        "Back": "to stand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 267
    },
    {
        "Front": "たて",
        "Back": "length,height",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "建物",
        "Back": "building",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 268
    },
    {
        "Front": "楽しい",
        "Back": "enjoyable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 269
    },
    {
        "Front": "頼む",
        "Back": "to ask",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 270
    },
    {
        "Front": "たぶん",
        "Back": "probably",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "たばこ",
        "Back": "tobacco,cigarettes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "食べ物",
        "Back": "food",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 271
    },
    {
        "Front": "食べる",
        "Back": "to eat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 272
    },
    {
        "Front": "卵",
        "Back": "egg",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 273
    },
    {
        "Front": "誰",
        "Back": "who",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 274
    },
    {
        "Front": "誕生日",
        "Back": "birthday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 275
    },
    {
        "Front": "だんだん",
        "Back": "gradually",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "小さい",
        "Back": "little",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 276
    },
    {
        "Front": "小さな",
        "Back": "little",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 277
    },
    {
        "Front": "近い",
        "Back": "near",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 278
    },
    {
        "Front": "違う",
        "Back": "to differ",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 279
    },
    {
        "Front": "近く",
        "Back": "near",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 280
    },
    {
        "Front": "地下鉄",
        "Back": "underground train",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 281
    },
    {
        "Front": "地図",
        "Back": "map",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 282
    },
    {
        "Front": "茶色",
        "Back": "brown",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 283
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちゃわん",
        "Back": "rice bowl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちょうど",
        "Back": "exactly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちょっと",
        "Back": "somewhat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "使う",
        "Back": "to use",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 284
    },
    {
        "Front": "疲れる",
        "Back": "to get tired",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 285
    },
    {
        "Front": "次",
        "Back": "next",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 286
    },
    {
        "Front": "着く",
        "Back": "to arrive at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 287
    },
    {
        "Front": "机",
        "Back": "desk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 288
    },
    {
        "Front": "作る",
        "Back": "to make",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 289
    },
    {
        "Front": "つける",
        "Back": "to turn on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "勤める",
        "Back": "to work for someone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 290
    },
    {
        "Front": "つまらない",
        "Back": "boring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷たい",
        "Back": "cold to the touch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 291
    },
    {
        "Front": "強い",
        "Back": "powerful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 292
    },
    {
        "Front": "手",
        "Back": "hand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 293
    },
    {
        "Front": "テープ",
        "Back": "tape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "テーブル",
        "Back": "table",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "テープレコーダー",
        "Back": "tape recorder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "出かける",
        "Back": "to go out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 294
    },
    {
        "Front": "手紙",
        "Back": "letter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 295
    },
    {
        "Front": "できる",
        "Back": "to be able to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "出口",
        "Back": "exit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 296
    },
    {
        "Front": "テスト",
        "Back": "test",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "では",
        "Back": "with that...",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "デパート",
        "Back": "department store",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "でも",
        "Back": "but",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "出る",
        "Back": "to appear,to leave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 297
    },
    {
        "Front": "テレビ",
        "Back": "television",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "天気",
        "Back": "weather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 298
    },
    {
        "Front": "電気",
        "Back": "electricity,electric light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 299
    },
    {
        "Front": "電車",
        "Back": "electric train",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 300
    },
    {
        "Front": "電話",
        "Back": "telephone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 301
    },
    {
        "Front": "戸",
        "Back": "Japanese style door",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 302
    },
    {
        "Front": "ドア",
        "Back": "Western style door",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "トイレ",
        "Back": "toilet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どう",
        "Back": "how,in what way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうして",
        "Back": "for what reason",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうぞ",
        "Back": "please",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "動物",
        "Back": "animal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 303
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうも",
        "Back": "thanks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "遠い",
        "Back": "far",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 304
    },
    {
        "Front": "十日",
        "Back": "ten days,the tenth day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 305
    },
    {
        "Front": "時々",
        "Back": "sometimes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 306
    },
    {
        "Front": "時計",
        "Back": "watch,clock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 307
    },
    {
        "Front": "どこ",
        "Back": "where",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "所",
        "Back": "place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 308
    },
    {
        "Front": "年",
        "Back": "year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 309
    },
    {
        "Front": "図書館",
        "Back": "library",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 310
    },
    {
        "Front": "どちら",
        "Back": "which of two",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どっち",
        "Back": "which",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "とても",
        "Back": "very",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どなた",
        "Back": "who",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "隣",
        "Back": "next door to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 311
    },
    {
        "Front": "どの",
        "Back": "which",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "飛ぶ",
        "Back": "to fly,to hop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 312
    },
    {
        "Front": "止まる",
        "Back": "to come to a halt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 313
    },
    {
        "Front": "友達",
        "Back": "friend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 314
    },
    {
        "Front": "土曜日",
        "Back": "Saturday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 315
    },
    {
        "Front": "鳥",
        "Back": "bird",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 316
    },
    {
        "Front": "とり肉",
        "Back": "chicken meat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 317
    },
    {
        "Front": "取る",
        "Back": "to take something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 318
    },
    {
        "Front": "撮る",
        "Back": "to take a photo or record a film",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 319
    },
    {
        "Front": "どれ",
        "Back": "which (of three or more)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ナイフ",
        "Back": "knife",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "中",
        "Back": "middle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 320
    },
    {
        "Front": "長い",
        "Back": "long",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 321
    },
    {
        "Front": "鳴く",
        "Back": "animal noise. to chirp, roar or croak etc.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 322
    },
    {
        "Front": "無くす",
        "Back": "to lose something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 323
    },
    {
        "Front": "なぜ",
        "Back": "why",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "夏",
        "Back": "summer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 324
    },
    {
        "Front": "夏休み",
        "Back": "summer holiday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 325
    },
    {
        "Front": "など",
        "Back": "et cetera",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "七つ",
        "Back": "seven",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 326
    },
    {
        "Front": "七日",
        "Back": "seven days,the seventh day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 327
    },
    {
        "Front": "名前",
        "Back": "name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 328
    },
    {
        "Front": "習う",
        "Back": "to learn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 329
    },
    {
        "Front": "並ぶ",
        "Back": "to line up,to stand in a line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 330
    },
    {
        "Front": "並べる",
        "Back": "to line up,to set up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 331
    },
    {
        "Front": "なる",
        "Back": "to become",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "何",
        "Back": "what",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 332
    },
    {
        "Front": "二",
        "Back": "two",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 333
    },
    {
        "Front": "賑やか",
        "Back": "bustling,busy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 334
    },
    {
        "Front": "肉",
        "Back": "meat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 335
    },
    {
        "Front": "西",
        "Back": "west",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 336
    },
    {
        "Front": "日曜日",
        "Back": "Sunday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 337
    },
    {
        "Front": "荷物",
        "Back": "luggage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 338
    },
    {
        "Front": "ニュース",
        "Back": "news",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "庭",
        "Back": "garden",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 339
    },
    {
        "Front": "脱ぐ",
        "Back": "to take off clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 340
    },
    {
        "Front": "温い",
        "Back": "luke warm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 341
    },
    {
        "Front": "ネクタイ",
        "Back": "tie,necktie",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "猫",
        "Back": "cat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 342
    },
    {
        "Front": "寝る",
        "Back": "to go to bed,to sleep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 343
    },
    {
        "Front": "ノート",
        "Back": "notebook,exercise book",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "登る",
        "Back": "to climb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 344
    },
    {
        "Front": "飲み物",
        "Back": "a drink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 345
    },
    {
        "Front": "飲む",
        "Back": "to drink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 346
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗る",
        "Back": "to get on,to ride",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 347
    },
    {
        "Front": "歯",
        "Back": "tooth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 348
    },
    {
        "Front": "パーティー",
        "Back": "party",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "はい",
        "Back": "yes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "灰皿",
        "Back": "ashtray",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 349
    },
    {
        "Front": "入る",
        "Back": "to enter,to contain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 350
    },
    {
        "Front": "葉書",
        "Back": "postcard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 351
    },
    {
        "Front": "はく",
        "Back": "to wear,to put on trousers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "箱",
        "Back": "box",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 352
    },
    {
        "Front": "橋",
        "Back": "bridge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 354
    },
    {
        "Front": "はし",
        "Back": "chopsticks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "始まる",
        "Back": "to begin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 353
    },
    {
        "Front": "初め/始め",
        "Back": "beginning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 355
    },
    {
        "Front": "初めて",
        "Back": "for the first time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 356
    },
    {
        "Front": "走る",
        "Back": "to run",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 357
    },
    {
        "Front": "バス",
        "Back": "bus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "バター",
        "Back": "butter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "二十歳",
        "Back": "20 years old,20th year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 358
    },
    {
        "Front": "働く",
        "Back": "to work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 359
    },
    {
        "Front": "八",
        "Back": "eight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 360
    },
    {
        "Front": "二十日",
        "Back": "twenty days,twentieth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 361
    },
    {
        "Front": "花",
        "Back": "flower",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 362
    },
    {
        "Front": "鼻",
        "Back": "nose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 363
    },
    {
        "Front": "話",
        "Back": "talk,story",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 364
    },
    {
        "Front": "話す",
        "Back": "to speak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 365
    },
    {
        "Front": "早い",
        "Back": "early",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 366
    },
    {
        "Front": "速い",
        "Back": "quick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 367
    },
    {
        "Front": "春",
        "Back": "spring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 368
    },
    {
        "Front": "貼る",
        "Back": "to stick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 369
    },
    {
        "Front": "晴れ",
        "Back": "clear weather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 370
    },
    {
        "Front": "晴れる",
        "Back": "to be sunny",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 371
    },
    {
        "Front": "半",
        "Back": "half",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 372
    },
    {
        "Front": "晩",
        "Back": "evening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 373
    },
    {
        "Front": "パン",
        "Back": "bread",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ハンカチ",
        "Back": "handkerchief",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "番号",
        "Back": "number",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 374
    },
    {
        "Front": "晩御飯",
        "Back": "evening meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 375
    },
    {
        "Front": "半分",
        "Back": "half minute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 376
    },
    {
        "Front": "東",
        "Back": "east",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 377
    },
    {
        "Front": "引く",
        "Back": "to pull",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 378
    },
    {
        "Front": "弾く",
        "Back": "to play an instrument with strings, including piano",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 379
    },
    {
        "Front": "低い",
        "Back": "short,low",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 380
    },
    {
        "Front": "飛行機",
        "Back": "aeroplane",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 381
    },
    {
        "Front": "左",
        "Back": "left hand side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 382
    },
    {
        "Front": "人",
        "Back": "person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 383
    },
    {
        "Front": "一つ",
        "Back": "one",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 384
    },
    {
        "Front": "一月",
        "Back": "one month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 385
    },
    {
        "Front": "一人",
        "Back": "one person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 386
    },
    {
        "Front": "暇",
        "Back": "free time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 387
    },
    {
        "Front": "百",
        "Back": "hundred",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 388
    },
    {
        "Front": "病院",
        "Back": "hospital",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 389
    },
    {
        "Front": "病気",
        "Back": "illness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 390
    },
    {
        "Front": "昼",
        "Back": "noon, daytime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 391
    },
    {
        "Front": "昼御飯",
        "Back": "midday meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 392
    },
    {
        "Front": "広い",
        "Back": "spacious,wide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 393
    },
    {
        "Front": "フィルム",
        "Back": "roll of film",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "封筒",
        "Back": "envelope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 394
    },
    {
        "Front": "プール",
        "Back": "swimming pool",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "フォーク",
        "Back": "fork",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "吹く",
        "Back": "to blow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 395
    },
    {
        "Front": "服",
        "Back": "clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 396
    },
    {
        "Front": "二つ",
        "Back": "two",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 397
    },
    {
        "Front": "豚肉",
        "Back": "pork",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 398
    },
    {
        "Front": "二人",
        "Back": "two people",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 399
    },
    {
        "Front": "二日",
        "Back": "two days, second day of the month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 400
    },
    {
        "Front": "太い",
        "Back": "fat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 401
    },
    {
        "Front": "冬",
        "Back": "winter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 402
    },
    {
        "Front": "降る",
        "Back": "to fall, e.g. rain or snow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 403
    },
    {
        "Front": "古い",
        "Back": "old (not used for people)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 404
    },
    {
        "Front": "ふろ",
        "Back": "bath",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "文章",
        "Back": "sentence,text",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 405
    },
    {
        "Front": "ページ",
        "Back": "page",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "下手",
        "Back": "unskillful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 406
    },
    {
        "Front": "ベッド",
        "Back": "bed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ペット",
        "Back": "pet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "部屋",
        "Back": "room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 407
    },
    {
        "Front": "辺",
        "Back": "area",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 408
    },
    {
        "Front": "ペン",
        "Back": "pen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "勉強",
        "Back": "to study",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 409
    },
    {
        "Front": "便利",
        "Back": "useful, convenient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 410
    },
    {
        "Front": "帽子",
        "Back": "hat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 411
    },
    {
        "Front": "ボールペン",
        "Back": "ball-point pen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ほか",
        "Back": "other, the rest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ポケット",
        "Back": "pocket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "欲しい",
        "Back": "want",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 412
    },
    {
        "Front": "ポスト",
        "Back": "post",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "細い",
        "Back": "thin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 413
    },
    {
        "Front": "ボタン",
        "Back": "button",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ホテル",
        "Back": "hotel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "本",
        "Back": "book",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 414
    },
    {
        "Front": "本棚",
        "Back": "bookshelves",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 415
    },
    {
        "Front": "ほんとう",
        "Back": "truth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "毎朝",
        "Back": "every morning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 416
    },
    {
        "Front": "毎月",
        "Back": "every month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 417
    },
    {
        "Front": "毎週",
        "Back": "every week",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 418
    },
    {
        "Front": "毎日",
        "Back": "every day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 419
    },
    {
        "Front": "毎年",
        "Back": "every year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 420
    },
    {
        "Front": "毎晩",
        "Back": "every night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 421
    },
    {
        "Front": "前",
        "Back": "before",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 422
    },
    {
        "Front": "曲る",
        "Back": "to turn,to bend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 423
    },
    {
        "Front": "まずい",
        "Back": "unpleasant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "また",
        "Back": "again,and",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "まだ",
        "Back": "yet,still",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "町",
        "Back": "town,city",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 424
    },
    {
        "Front": "待つ",
        "Back": "to wait",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 425
    },
    {
        "Front": "まっすぐ",
        "Back": "straight ahead,direct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "マッチ",
        "Back": "match",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "窓",
        "Back": "window",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 426
    },
    {
        "Front": "丸い/円い",
        "Back": "round,circular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 427
    },
    {
        "Front": "万",
        "Back": "ten thousand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 428
    },
    {
        "Front": "万年筆",
        "Back": "fountain pen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 429
    },
    {
        "Front": "磨く",
        "Back": "to brush teeth, to polish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 430
    },
    {
        "Front": "右",
        "Back": "right side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 431
    },
    {
        "Front": "短い",
        "Back": "short",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 432
    },
    {
        "Front": "水",
        "Back": "water",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 433
    },
    {
        "Front": "店",
        "Back": "shop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 434
    },
    {
        "Front": "見せる",
        "Back": "to show",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 435
    },
    {
        "Front": "道",
        "Back": "street",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 436
    },
    {
        "Front": "三日",
        "Back": "three days, third day of the month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 437
    },
    {
        "Front": "三つ",
        "Back": "three",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 438
    },
    {
        "Front": "緑",
        "Back": "green",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 439
    },
    {
        "Front": "皆さん",
        "Back": "everyone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 440
    },
    {
        "Front": "南",
        "Back": "south",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 441
    },
    {
        "Front": "耳",
        "Back": "ear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 442
    },
    {
        "Front": "見る&nbsp;&nbsp;観る",
        "Back": "to see, to watch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 443
    },
    {
        "Front": "みんな",
        "Back": "everyone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "六日",
        "Back": "six days, sixth day of the month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 444
    },
    {
        "Front": "向こう",
        "Back": "over there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 445
    },
    {
        "Front": "難しい",
        "Back": "difficult",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 446
    },
    {
        "Front": "六つ",
        "Back": "six",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 447
    },
    {
        "Front": "村",
        "Back": "village",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 448
    },
    {
        "Front": "目",
        "Back": "eye",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 449
    },
    {
        "Front": "メートル",
        "Back": "metre",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "眼鏡",
        "Back": "glasses",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 450
    },
    {
        "Front": "もう",
        "Back": "already",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "もう一度",
        "Back": "again",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 451
    },
    {
        "Front": "木曜日",
        "Back": "Thursday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 452
    },
    {
        "Front": "持つ",
        "Back": "to hold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 453
    },
    {
        "Front": "もっと",
        "Back": "more",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "物",
        "Back": "thing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 454
    },
    {
        "Front": "門",
        "Back": "gate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 455
    },
    {
        "Front": "問題",
        "Back": "problem",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 456
    },
    {
        "Front": "八百屋",
        "Back": "greengrocer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 457
    },
    {
        "Front": "野菜",
        "Back": "vegetable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 458
    },
    {
        "Front": "易しい",
        "Back": "easy, simple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 459
    },
    {
        "Front": "安い",
        "Back": "cheap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 460
    },
    {
        "Front": "休み",
        "Back": "rest,holiday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 461
    },
    {
        "Front": "休む",
        "Back": "to rest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 462
    },
    {
        "Front": "八つ",
        "Back": "eight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 463
    },
    {
        "Front": "山",
        "Back": "mountain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 464
    },
    {
        "Front": "やる",
        "Back": "to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "夕方",
        "Back": "evening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 465
    },
    {
        "Front": "夕飯",
        "Back": "dinner",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 466
    },
    {
        "Front": "郵便局",
        "Back": "post office",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 467
    },
    {
        "Front": "昨夜",
        "Back": "last night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 468
    },
    {
        "Front": "有名",
        "Back": "famous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 469
    },
    {
        "Front": "雪",
        "Back": "snow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 470
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゆっくりと",
        "Back": "slowly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "八日",
        "Back": "eight days, eighth day of the month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 471
    },
    {
        "Front": "洋服",
        "Back": "western-style clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 472
    },
    {
        "Front": "よく",
        "Back": "often, well",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "横",
        "Back": "beside,side,width",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 473
    },
    {
        "Front": "四日",
        "Back": "four days, fouth day of the month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 474
    },
    {
        "Front": "四つ",
        "Back": "four",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 475
    },
    {
        "Front": "呼ぶ",
        "Back": "to call out,to invite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 476
    },
    {
        "Front": "読む",
        "Back": "to read",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 477
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜",
        "Back": "evening,night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 478
    },
    {
        "Front": "弱い",
        "Back": "weak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 479
    },
    {
        "Front": "来月",
        "Back": "next month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 480
    },
    {
        "Front": "来週",
        "Back": "next week",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 481
    },
    {
        "Front": "来年",
        "Back": "next year",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 482
    },
    {
        "Front": "ラジオ",
        "Back": "radio",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ラジカセ / ラジオカセット",
        "Back": "radio cassette player",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "りっぱ",
        "Back": "splendid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "留学生",
        "Back": "overseas student",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 483
    },
    {
        "Front": "両親",
        "Back": "both parents",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 484
    },
    {
        "Front": "料理",
        "Back": "cuisine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 485
    },
    {
        "Front": "旅行",
        "Back": "travel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 486
    },
    {
        "Front": "零",
        "Back": "zero",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 487
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷蔵庫",
        "Back": "refrigerator",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 488
    },
    {
        "Front": "レコード",
        "Back": "record",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レストラン",
        "Back": "restaurant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "練習",
        "Back": "to practice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 489
    },
    {
        "Front": "廊下",
        "Back": "corridor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 490
    },
    {
        "Front": "六",
        "Back": "six",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 491
    },
    {
        "Front": "ワイシャツ",
        "Back": "business shirt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "若い",
        "Back": "young",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 492
    },
    {
        "Front": "分かる",
        "Back": "to be understood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 493
    },
    {
        "Front": "忘れる",
        "Back": "to forget",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 494
    },
    {
        "Front": "私",
        "Back": "(humble) I,myself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 495
    },
    {
        "Front": "渡す",
        "Back": "to hand over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 496
    },
    {
        "Front": "渡る",
        "Back": "to go across",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 497
    },
    {
        "Front": "悪い",
        "Back": "bad",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 498
    },
    {
        "Front": "より、ほう",
        "Back": "Used for comparison.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    }
]